Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
- Series IX. Events and classes
  - Staff standing in aisle of medical records unit, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    Item number: 751008-2-34
  - Sheep being examining in stall; one person records data (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Item number: 307.1
  - Outdoor clinic; people in white standing; Dr. Walter L Williams in derby hat (2nd from left), 1906 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Item number: 336.4
  - Outdoor clinic; people in white standing; Dr. Walter L Williams (barely visible in center in derby hat and white clothes), 1906 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Item number: 336.41
  - Clinician adjusting a equipment near a cow, Undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Item number: 317.2
  - Cattle with horse in barn, Undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Flock of sheep lined up in stalls outside with person in coveralls, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Item number: 7615-11
  - Flock of sheep in field in summer with person in coveralls carrying a pail, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Item number: 7615-12
  - 4 men in coveralls trimming rear hoof of Holstein cow, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Item number: 7615-8
  - Students in Medical Clinic amphitheater with horse being examined by a man in white coat (left) and woman in white coveralls (right), Undated (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Dr Francis Fox (2nd from left) with 2 students examining a horse's eye, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Item number: 7615-39
  - Dr. Donald Delahanty (2nd from right with arm raised) with Robert Cook (in white lab coat) and Gordon Layton and E Neil Moore examining the leg of a horse outside the old surgery building and Barton Hall in background, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Item number: 7615-4
  - Students John Jeffries (left) and Peter Hall (right) walk a large bull on driveway behind veterinary school, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Item number: 61-10-10-13
  - Dr. Karl K White (standing in white) with 3 students (Bill Thomson kneeling) with Holstein cow in paddock behind Large Animal Clinic, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Item number: 761001-6-13
  - Dr. John E Lowe examining some horses in paddock, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Item number: 761001-26-10
  - Dr. Stephen Dill (right) examining a horse in a paddock, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Dr Susan Fubini (2nd from right bending over) wsith students examining a horse, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    Item number: 840107-26-20A
  - Clinician testing udders of Jersey cow in barn with milk collection pails and milking pump in foreground, Undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Dr John E Lowe with students inputting nasal tube in horse, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Item number: 741023-4-36A
  - Dr John E Lowe (right jacket) with student in corral with horses, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Item number: 741023-4-17
  - Head of Dr. Peyton ( no animals ), 1974 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Item number: 741023-17-24A
  - Dr Robert Whitlock with Harry Abair and Doug Midlan outside Large Animal Clinic, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Item number: 741023-14-21A
  - Dr Ingram and Dr Peyton with David Campbell looking at radiographs, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Item number: 741023-15-25
  - Clinician and student looking at Holstein cow in stachions, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Item number: 751008-4-20
  - Clinician and student treat a Holstein cow, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Item number: 751008-4-21
  - Students in bovine clinic area, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Item number: 751008-16-5A
  - Clinician and 2 students in bovine clinic with two cows in stanchions, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Item number: 780407-15-28A
  - Dr Stephen Dill listens to heart of a light colored horse, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Item number: 780701-1-18A
  - Man leads Holstein cow in driveway behind Schurman Hall on east side of Veterinary Research Tower, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Item number: 78051501-10
  - Joe Mankowski holding bridle of horses head, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Student holding lead of a large draft horse in breezeway, 1988 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    Item number: 48
  - Dorothy Schenck (large animal technician) rubbing nose of horse, Undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Clinician in light-colored coveralls listening to heart of a newborn foal, Undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Student (Joe Mankowski?) in dark-colored coveralls scratching head of newborn foal, Undated (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Dr N Sydney Moise (left) listening to heart of dark horse with veterinary student, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Dr. Howard J Milks (right) with Dr. Hadley Stephenson?? (left) examining a greyhound dog with a fractured front right leg, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Item number: 332.2
  - Clinician examining an anesthetized dogs on a operating table, Undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Five men in whites examining Beagle dogs on 3 tables, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Item number: 4599-D
  - Dr. Herb Bandemer (far left) with 5 students (one byDr. Tas Dueland) examining Beagle dogs on 3 tables, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Item number: 7615-6
  - Dr. Stephen Roberts (3rd from right in center) with 5 students building wooden cages in Medical Building 1955 7615-35, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Item number: 7615-35
  - Dr. Stephen Roberts with stethoscope listing to heart of dog held by man in dark suit observed by 6 students in white coats, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Item number: 7615-7
  - Woman with greyhound dog at reception room window in Small Animal Clinic, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Item number: 4599-H
  - Three clinicians examine a dachshund dog on table in SA clinic, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Item number: 4599-E
  - Dr. Jack Geary (right) and 2 students look at radiographs, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Item number: 7615-15
  - Clinicians in coveralls giving puppy dog an injection, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Item number: 5870-K
  - Five students in green coveralls outside Schurman with a dog on a leash, Undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Nine students in white examining a white rabbit on a lab bench, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    Item number: 7615-16
  - Three students looking at X-rays, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 5-50-74
  - Kennel area with attendant at end of row, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 741023-2-31A
  - Clinician with clients examining a dog in Exam Room 3, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 741023-1-11
  - Students Steve Van Wie and Doug Aspros bathing a Spaniel dog and holding bowl of water, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 741023-15-37
  - Technicians preparing anesthetized dog for radiographs, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 741023-2-26A
  - Clinician and student with clients examining a dog, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 741023-1-17
  - Technician guiding a bandages black cat, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 751008-16-15A
  - Student bandaging right forepaw of a terrier dog, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 751008-20-13A
  - Student listening to heart of German Shepherd dog with two children watching, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 751008-2-23
  - Student holding a hound-type dog on lap, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 751008-17-30
  - Student Phil Deitsch holding paw and head of mixed-breed dog, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 751008-16-21A
  - Two students reading ECG printout with shepherd-type dog, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 751008-17-11
  - Student holding neck of a German Shepherd dog, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 751008-16-11A
  - Student holding head of Great Dane dog with a second dog up close, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 751008-17-32
  - Two students look at medical records chart with "Exam Room 2" sign on door behind, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 751008-7-22
  - Two students -- one recording notes and the other looking in a dog's mouth, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 751008-6-5
  - Groups of students with clinician in white performing treatment on dogs on two tables, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 751008-19-9 and 9A
  - Two students discussing dog on table, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 751008-17-13
  - Students performing treatments on dogs in clinic; Carolyn McMaster in center, 1978 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 780407-6-19A
  - Two students taking ECG of the setter dog on a table, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 790802-15-21A
  - Dr. Gary R. Bolton (right) with student performing ECG on terrier dog, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: #1-30-80
  - Student holding a shaggy dog on a table, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: A10104-9-34
  - Student bathing a puppy with a protective Elizabethan collar, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: A10104-2-31
  - Student Carol Carberry holding hound dog near inhalation apparatus, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: A20503-53-34A
  - Student Carol Carberry using stethoscope on a hound dog on a table, 1982 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: A20503-3-7A
  - Student Chris Murphy with client examining a tiger cat, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 830204-20-33
  - Three students performing procedure on large dog, 1983 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 830103-17-36
  - Student Sylvester Price listening to a dog's heart, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: 840107-44-8
  - Resident Dr Laratta with student looks into dog's eye, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Dr Donna Walton examines a dog's ear, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    Item number: PR5-14-85B3
  - Clinician with long hair has two white parrots on her shoulder and in kennel (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Student Deborah Fisher holds a tiger cat, Undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Student looks at head of black Great Dane dog, 1987 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Student with heavy sweater hold a lab dog on leash on wall, Undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Clinician in white lab coat holding tiger cat facing left, Undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Woman with braided hair looking at Spaniel dog with student in clinic, Undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Students in microbiology lab in James Law Hall, 1903 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    Item number: 3-183-86
  - Students in bacteriology lab in Moore Lab, 1940 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    Item number: 311.2
  - Students in bacteriology lab in Moore Lab, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    Item number: 7615-9
  - Students in microbiology lab in James Law Hall, 1900 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Two people in white coats with timing Beagle laying on table, Undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Machine to record ECG with Beagle dog at top, Undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Man in white coat looking at equipment with Beagle dog laying on table in foreground, Undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Man in white coat in center adjusting equipment with two technicians and Beagle dog on table, Undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Technician with equipment and anesthetized Beagle dog on table, Undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Technician adjusts equipment on counter, Undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Veterinary students necropsying a cow carcass in Moore Lab (duplicate from Dr Donald W Baker Photograph Collection), 1950 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    Item number: 424
  - Dr John M King (right) demonstrated necropsyof a dog to 4 students (Charlie Reid, E Neal, Moore), 1955 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    Item number: 7615-17
  - Parasitology lab with class of 1934 students; horse intestines on floor; Prof. Dr. Donald W Baker (lower right) in fedora hat, 1934 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Students in pathology lab in James Law Hall, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    Item number: 311.21
  - Students in pathology lab in Moore Lab (A deLahunta, Lougnelty?), 1955 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    Item number: 7615-13
  - Students in microbiology lab in Moore lab, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    Item number: 7613-13
  - Students looking at notes near microscope (Box 46, Folder 17)
    Item number: 10212-8-15
  - Dr. Lennart Krook (right) and Dr. Chineme looking at microscopes, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    Item number: 741023-28-16
  - Rows of students at lab benches looking through microscopes, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    Item number: 741023-10-5
  - Student with glasses looking through microscope, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    Item number: 761001-32-25A
  - Two students looking through double-head microscope, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    Item number: 761001-32-29A
  - Dr Lois Roth (left) with another student looking though double-headed microscope, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    Item number: 761001-32=34A
  - Students in pathology lab looking at Dr. Charles Rickard in white lab coat, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    Item number: 761001-32-14A
  - Dr. Charles G Rickard (left) explaining to students in pathology lab at microscopes, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 17)
    Item number: 761001-32-22A
  - Dr Malcolm E Peckham innoculating a test tube in the poultry diagnostic laboratory in Moore Lab, 1954 (Box 46, Folder 19)
    Item number: 6238-A
  - Dr. Mitchell performing procedure on white chicken observed by 5 men in suits, Undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
    Item number: 650-11
  - Pigeon in a sling in bandaged legs, Undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Two men in white dissecting a chicken in the poultry diagnostic laboratory, Undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Poultry diagnostic lab in Moore Lab; Dr. Malcolm Peckham (2nd from right); Dr. Philip Pincus Levine (right), Undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Worker (Dr. Angstom?) in lab coat putting test tubes into an incubation chamber; in the poultry diagnostic lab?, Undated (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Dr Daniel Tapper in physiology lab in Schurman Hall, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    Item number: 8717-10
  - Dr David Hughes with complete dog carcass in Dr. Herbert Gilman's lab in James Law Hall, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    Item number: 7290-A
  - Dr David Hughes with partially dissected dog carcass in Dr Herbert Gilman's lab in James Hall Hall, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    Item number: 7290-B
  - Dr Dougherty with two assistants working on a sheep carcass, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    Item number: 7615-26
  - Dr Lou Nangroni with 3 students and physiology apparatus (Harry Russell, Erwin Pierson), 1955 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    Item number: 7615-36
  - Five persons viewing physiology apparatus (Don Eno, Dan Tapper? (3rd from right), Dick Cressey), 1955 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    Item number: 7615-38
  - Dr. H Hugh Dukes (left) and Dr Myron G Fincher (2nd from right) with 4 students conducting experiment on live cow (Bob Cook, Herb Tanger, MG Feinheim, Bob Squires), 1955 (Box 46, Folder 18)
    Item number: 7615-32
  - Dr. H Hugh Dukes (left) and Dr Myron G Fincher (2rd from right) with 4 students conducting experiment on live cow (Bob Cook, Herb Tanger, MG Feinheim, Bob Squires), 1955 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Three men looking a horse head on operating table; Darby (1907), Miller (Dr Williams' assistant), Drew (1906?), 1906 (Box 46)
    Item number: 341.11
  - Dr Walter L Williams (center derby hat) and Dr. James Frost operating on a horse with many students, 1906 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Item number: 341.12
  - Clinician performing a surgical procedure on a horses head viewed by 6 students, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Item number: 341.3
  - Dr Walter L Williams (2nd from left) surgery class with 5 students standing behind an empty surgery table, 1905-1920 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Item number: 341.22
  - Dr Walter L Williams (2nd from right) with 5 students standing behind a horse on an operating table in the surgery building, 1905-1920 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Item number: 3-151-86
  - Three men in white with horse upside down on operating table; Taylor, Miller (Dr. Williams' assistant) and Wright doing thesis on roaring in horses, 1906 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Item number: 341.21
  - Dr A Gordon Danks (2nd from left) with 9 students performing surgery on a recumbant horse, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Item number: 7615-21
  - Surgeon operating on a draped recumbant horse viewed by 9 students with overhead lamp, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Item number: 7615-42
  - Surgeon operating on a draped horse viewed by 5 students and an overhead lamp, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Item number: 7615-41
  - Dr. James Law (center in brimed hat) preparing for surgery on a recumbent horse with many white suited men, 1900 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Dr. James Law (3rd from right in brimed hat) during operation on a horse's leg with many white suited men, 1900 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Dr. Walter L Williams (2nd from right) during operation on head of a recumbant horse, 1900 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Group 27 students standing outside behind James Law Hall and Clinic buildings doing surgery on a recumbent horse, 1914 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Item number: 8-73-93
  - Horse being slid down from operating table with 9 students in white in surgery building, Undated (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Item number: 377
  - Two surgeons operating on a large animal, probably a draped horse, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Item number: 741209-1-13
  - Veterinary students in 3-year (junior) surgery, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Item number: 840107-20-18
  - Dr Michael Collier (right) explaining to veterinary student gowned for surgery, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 20)
    Item number: 840107-19-10A
  - Dr Howard J Milks (center) with students and surgical cases, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    Item number: 331
  - Dr. Ellis P Leonard performing surgery observed by 6 persons, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    Item number: 7615-20
  - Dr. Ellis P Leonard observing surgery on a dog in small animal clinic, Undated (Box 46, Folder 21)
    Item number: 18144
  - Four surgeons operating on a dog, Undated (Box 46, Folder 21)
    Item number: 4-96-92
  - Two surgeons operating with hemostats around a draped incision, Undated (Box 46, Folder 21)
    Item number: 15639
  - Four surgeons check instruments in operating room, Undated (Box 46, Folder 21)
    Item number: 5-138-83
  - Five surgeons operating on a cat, 1949 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    Item number: 4599-C
  - One surgeon operating on a dog with lamp pole in center, Undated (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - One surgeon operating on a dog with lamp pole on right, Undated (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Surgeons during an operation; irrigation bottle in foreground, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    Item number: 741023-3-36
  - Three gowned and masked surgeons operating on a draped smalll animal., 1984 (Box 46, Folder 21)
    Item number: 840107-20-4
  - Three students including Ann Sturmer gowned in junior surgery [Includes 3 photo discs], 1990 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Two students doing rectal exam, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    Item number: 761001-10-6
  - Student with gloved arm, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    Item number: 761001-10-15
  - Two students with gloved arms, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    Item number: 761001-10-20
  - Dr. Charles Hall looking at specimens with Dr. Charles Guard, students, and Dr. Robert Hillman., 1984 (Box 46, Folder 22)
    Item number: 840107-28-11A
  - Mr Block in laboratory, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    Item number: 761001-36-11
  - Dr Melissa Woan in laboratory, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 23)
    Item number: 840108-4-4A
  - Dr James A Baker key scientist in the lapinized vaccine development, Undated (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Cornell Research Laboratory for Diseases of Dogs, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Dr James Baker and 3 others with dedication plaques, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Technican Ron Wolverton repairing a printer in Biomedical Electronics, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    Item number: A11110-2-13A
  - Veterinary Computing work room with Dr. Fred Scott (right), 1974 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    Item number: 4-403-74
  - Computers in Veterinary Research Tower, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 24)
    Item number: 741023-24-35
  - Student fitting a shoe with head of horse looking on, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 25)
    Item number: 790802-8-3
  - Dr. Fred Quimby with two technicians examining a Beagle dog in laboratory animal medicine services, 1981 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    Item number: A10212-5-3
  - Paul Smith examining a white rabbit in laboratory animal medicine services, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    Item number: 741023-32-22A
  - Jim Hayden and Linda Byer with white rabbit in laboratory animal medicine services, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    Item number: 741023-25-25A
  - Jim Hayden and Linda Byer with white rabbit in laboratory animal medicine services, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    Item number: 741023-25-29A
  - Two techicians inoculating a white mouse in laboratory animal medicine services, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    Item number: 741023-25-15A
  - Technician holding a rabbit in laboratory animal medicine services (Box 46, Folder 26)
    Item number: A11110-3-20
  - Two technicians with bitch and puppies in laboratory animal medicine services, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    Item number: 741023-19-5A
  - John Gilmartin (left) with 2 technicians holding Beagle puppies in laboratory animal medicine services, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    Item number: 761001-41-29
  - John Gilmartin (right) with technican in masks holding white mice in laboratory animal medicine services, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    Item number: 761001-42-35
  - Beagle dog in cage in laboratory animal medicine services, 1980 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Debbie Alo holding a puppy in laboratory animal medicine services, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 26)
    Item number: 790802-23-23A
  - Technician holding a woodchuck in Specific Pathogen Free colony, Undated (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Dr Gary Dunny with technician in microbiology lab, 1984 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    Item number: 840107-3-8A
  - Two technicians in microbiology lab in Veterinary Research Tower, 1979 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    Item number: 790802-2-29A
  - Microbiology tissue culture lab, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 27)
    Item number: 72-1xx
  - Two rooms with scanning electron microscopes in the Pathology Department in the Veterinary Research Tower, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 28)
    Item number: 741023-28-32
  - Linda Buier holding a white rabbit in a pathology lab, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 28)
    Item number: 741023-25-221A
  - Two technicans working with pathology slides, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 28)
    Item number: 751008-11-12
  - Ann Rothermick and Roger Ellis handling mouse in pathology lab, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 28)
    Item number: 741023-25-13A
  - Three rows of men seated and standing. Dr. Cyril Comar seated in center in white jacket, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Two rows of men and women standing in front of Schurman Hall entrance, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    Item number: 59-7-24-5
  - Scientist looking through microscope doing surgical procedure on the back of a cat, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    Item number: 64-5-14-1
  - Scientist pushing a woman on gurney into a scanning chamber observed by another scientist, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    Item number: 61-11-8-2
  - Physical Biology building on Snyder Hall with cars in front, Undated (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Two views of an unidentified man; one front of the door to Schurman Hall, Undated (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Dr Curtis Fullmer in physical biology laboratory, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    Item number: 741023-24-19
  - Kim Messersmith in computer lab, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    Item number: 741023-24-36
  - Radiation biology laboratory for handling and counting radionuclides, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Manipulating gamma cells for radiation exposure, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Two scientists in laboratory with radiobiology equipment, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 29)
    Item number: 72-6-22-3
  - Taking blood from a pig to produce hog cholera vaccine at the Veterinary Experiment Station, 1920 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Dr. Raymond R Birch taking blood from a pig in a cradle from hog cholera vaccine production at the Veterinary Experiment Station, 1920 (Box 46, Folder 30)
- Series X. Faculty and Staff